SEAN TOSELLO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I'm a seasoned academic and educator with experience training large language models and building responsive web applications. I bring a high standard of excellence, a persistent passion for learning, and an enthusiasm for engineering innovative solutions.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END ENGINEER

(2023 - Present)

Freelance

- Utilize React.js, JavaScript (ES6)., HTML. CSS, and Python
- Built portfolio website in React.js with custom Scripting and CSS
- Integrated Yelp API in "ravenous" project
- · Optimize Performance with automated and manual testing

AI CONTENT QUALITY EXPERT

(2024 - Present)

Outlier

- Evaluate AI-generated writing.
- Provide detailed feedback to refine LLMs
- Review and critique the work of fellow human writers
- Test AI models with diverse prompts
- Assess the End-User Experience of LLMs

HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER

(2021 - 2024)

Capistrano Valley Christian Schools

- Built innovative "Cultural Cornerstone" project
- Researched best industry practices to optimize user (student) experience
- Collaborated with stakeholders

CREATIVE DIRECTOR

(2018 - 2020)

Deep River Books

- Increased website traffic through improved SEO and UX
- Coordinated with external contractors in product development
- Communicated with clients on product development updates and implementing client requests

CONTACT

541-390-6726

 \checkmark

sean.l.tosello@gmail.com

0

Orange County, CA



seantosello.com

lin

linkedin.com/in/sean-tosello

SKILLS

- React.js, JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS, Git
- Custom Scripting and CSS
- React Hooks / API Integration
- SQL / MySQL
- Gen AI Large Language Models
- Technical Troubleshooting

EDUCATION

MASTER OF ARTS

Biola University

2020-2021

BACHELOR OF ARTS

Biola University

2010 - 2016